good morning and mutable b-ball I as
always so 24 hours since I came online
so much has happened I woke up again
priests exam to have a conversation with
three men this morning now I'm on here
for an hour and then there's the idea
cafe laters
before noon before 11:00 a.m. really I
will have been on video chat for over
three hours miss Raymond my conversation
was an hour and 20 minutes but things
are coming together yesterday after my
session where I talked about like what
are we gonna do during this hour I had
the Epiphany that these hours aren't
really working for me because I don't
like broadcast I don't like coming on
and talking for an hour I'm not really
great at it I don't get the interaction
I would like like I'm not fueled by it
in fact it takes energy doesn't give
energy and coming to that realization
realizing that one of the reasons I was
looking hot during the day was partly to
recover from these hours but I'm still
showing up I'm still putting my button
the seat because there's a there wasn't
anything better at the moment and so
that is my deal with the universe so I'm
gonna keep listening until something
else comes out I'm also right now
because I've been smoking pot during the
day I'm just like yep that is how life
is right now but the first hour after
I've smoked the pot I'm cleaning my
house
so yesterday right after the broadcast
I smoked pot and was cleaning my kitchen
and it was like the most obvious
solution I'm not gonna do seven days a
week of broadcast I'm gonna continue for
there till the end of this week doing
what I had planned and then next week
possibly gonna take the week off and
then the following week I will be back
with four different conversations that
take place at the same time every day of
the week but a completely different
conversation besides the fact that I'm
part of it all of them on this channel
so one day we probably on Wednesday it's
that's already on Wednesday so I'll be
doing the solution raising exactly like
what it's looked like where we have
whoever shows up shows up and has an
hour-long conversation where we generate
a jacent possible solution that we could
implement right now if we had 10,000
people and $100,000 the other thing I've
been looking for over the last month of
doing
but haven't quite figured out how to get
but it's coming together is people to
due process raising with so in the
solution Racing's we come up with
amazing ideas but we're not actually
creating them in the world we're just
generating the idea so with process
raising what I'm looking to do is
brainstorm an actual process that we
could try out with more than what can
fit on the screen right with more than
six people
preferably ten thousand people's we can
get ten thousand people and have a
hundred thousand dollars but what could
that process look like so looking for
people to work through that process with
both the generation of how that process
could look and then actually trying it
out with as many people as our
capability that with and then
continually improving the process to
work with more people and to get better
and do that whole thing transparently
we're still going to have all these
conversations live online because I
think it is important for several
reasons which we're also coming to me
but I forgot to write down but doing
them live online both brings in people
but it show it gives people hope that
these conversations are happening and
they're invited to be part of them some
people just want to know the
conversations are happening that other
people are dealing with that how great
there are other people having these big
conversations but I think there's a
large section of the population who's
looking exactly for game B even if they
don't know gate B exists they're looking
for something that they can participate
in fully bring all of their ideas to and
so that between the four conversations
or four conversations I want to have
every week and if they so what I'm
looking for is a group of people for
each of them that will continually show
up every week so I don't have to try to
get people to come there it works out
fairly good for the solution raising of
a handful of people who show up quite
regularly it's same with the idea cafe I
stopped trying to get people to come
there and like people that show up we
just won't host them but I really do
want three to four other people for each
of these conversations who are gonna
continually show up so the worse that
happens is one or two people show up and
then other people are invited to come
and participate as well so again it'll
be solution raised and exactly like it
has been we pick a topic and we talk
about what currently happens under
transportation or healthcare
whatever the topic is that week's panel
over my hand my vinick's photo second
reign with the sorority and then 15
minutes talking about our utopian ideal
5 10 100 years in the future in under
that same umbrella it doesn't need to
match between us and they spend the vast
majority the 30 minutes of time talking
about what we could actually create
right now if we had 10,000 people and
hundred thousand dollars and we've
started at the end of the solution
raisings having a quick round of what
the individual thinks is the most
powerful thing we've talked about what
did they think it has the most potential
for the 10,000 people in 100,000 dollars
so then I'm looking to create process
raising which will be the most
vulnerable and like awkward because
we're gonna be figuring it out on camera
while we're figuring it out right like
what could a process look like what
could a governance look like having a
conversation about finance have any
conversation about marketing and having
conversation about brainstorming what
could that process look like so we might
do a solution raising our noses raising
it and I'm just trying different things
and see how that works the other to
quiet conversations that I want to have
every week one of which is the five
questions I have been doing them with
the idea cafe in fact later on on its
own channel will be having the fourth of
five conversations we're talking about
the fourth question which is what do I
need today and so what I want to do is
have what we kind of like what we've
been doing with the idea cafe where
either we're cycling through the five
questions every week it's a different
question we just keep cycling through
them but as is the point of the five
questions you you never answer them
which is why five weeks later is gonna
be a different answer Who am I
the next day it's gonna be a different
answer like what's my purpose these are
questions that like the purpose of life
is answer is to try to answer them and
never answer them the journey towards
answering them Who am I who are my
people what is my purpose what do I need
and what am I ready to let go of and so
I'm looking to participate in those
fightin in a group who want to explore
those five questions weekly hopefully
it's burns other people to want to start
their own
to answer it but the idea with that one
is that it's like the same just like my
Omega group that it's the same people
who show up we have the week so you get
to know each other and whatever audience
is there can get to know us as well to
see what it looks like to do the inner
personal work in interpersonal that
there is ways that aren't just
meditation that do involve a
conversation circling is a great tool
it's like that but I want I want to
explore these five questions because
they came through me there's something
about them that is like wow this is for
me it's the secret of life it's like to
answer these five questions and
continually know that I never will and
that's okay it's just about continually
looking at them and saying hey Who am I
who are my people what is my purpose
what do I need and what am I ready to
let go of so that is the third question
the third conversation I'm looking to
have weekly and I don't yet know what
day of the week these are gonna be on
but I want them to be the same time
across the board just like this is 8:30
am if 8:30 a.m. works then and will
continue at that time otherwise it might
change to 7:00 a.m. might change tonight
a.m. depending on when other people are
available that the one had this
conversation the fourth question are the
fourth topic of conversation is just a
conversation I enjoy having and it seems
to come up in the game be space a lot
and so to actually just put an umbrella
on it and it's like the power of
technology what we can create together
it's technology so it's just an hour big
eek out it's not about necessarily
creating anything during that hour it's
just about sharing our special interest
sharing that people who care about
technology in any way that they can see
the power they can see the the potential
of what we can do together so that would
be things like cryptocurrency and
blockchain which honestly I don't
understand that well the point is that
you have to understand technology to
come participate but that that is a
topic you want to talk about right the
power of technology and what we can
create together with it and so I'm going
to be writing up the five questions is a
little more arduous EFT explain the five
questions and why purpose of life
is to continually ask them I never
answer them so people kind of get an
idea and then linked to the idea cafes
that we've been doing and say this is
basically what I want to do but on a
weekly basis the process we're using I
don't know what it looks like the point
is everyone has their own individual
governance and marketing and Finance of
their own thing that they're trying to
they're trying to create basically
talked out even though we're creating it
for the public well we had people we
could change it but it's our individual
brains are sitting alone and coming up
with it and if what does that process
look like doing it together because
we've all done it
individually singularly but not as a
collective what does it look like to let
go of my ego and my version of how
government should be my version of how
we should finance it what is the and
actually work through what could we
create as a system of creation with
10,000 people and then try it it up like
I said and working through it live on
camera so that there is radical
transparency and then having the I want
to have those four conversations every
week and it will I show up differently
in a conversation than I do in broadcast
and there's something about it I don't
know whether I will add a fifth a fifth
day of the week in order to just
broadcast because I am still trying to
trying might be the wrong word hoping
hoping that my communication style will
improve well so demanding that it does
and so there is something about coming
on and practicing speaking for my heart
but what it's seven days a week and it's
an hour I actually I'm not doing that
that's why the try is it a little bit of
a try it might be a little bit out of
range but I believe in the game be space
it'll be more than enough people who
want to talk about the power of
Technology every week it's just about
brainstorming that's why I'm taking the
week off is picking a day getting the
people and brainstorming what that could
look like right what what conversations
we want to have let the power of tech
over the next four weeks and then decide
be the next four weeks the next four
weeks the five questions the five
questions already done it's just to go
through the five questions and then on
the sixth week do we do medic medic
question like do we just and continue or
do we cycle through every every time
right because when you're answering Who
am I your purpose and your people come
into it and what you need comes into it
and vice versa so even though there's
one that you're concentrating on that
week you're really answering all of them
so whether we just honor that and answer
all of them whichever one you want to
answer that week or we cycle through
them it doesn't actually matter which
one we do you're answering them all
anyway and then looking for particular
people to due process raising with
people who this is something they want
to do that they are similar to me that
they've sat alone and self whole world's
problems alone in their bedroom now how
do we do that together with the very
particular umbrella um parameters of I
want to concentrate on finding a system
of creation for ten thousand people both
how do we get the ten thousand people
and then how do we create with ten
thousand people where they feel like
they're empowered they feel like they
also own the project so that they are
natural marketers and have the energy of
ownership but they feel that they can
co-create solutions so they can find
problems that they can they can design
together that they it's our project not
my project right like to create that
ownership in it but it being ownership
ownership that's meatball we own it know
are the person gone almost like
screaming or screeching I don't like
that actual it's my kid hurt no I know
this out of my kitty hurt
weirdly oh there's my kid come out of
the room